Ronstadt family collection, 1802-1993 (bulk 1880-1960)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Ronstadt family collection, 1802-1993 (bulk 1880-1960)
MS 407
Ronstadt family
Collection 1802-1993 (bulk 1880-1960). The Ronstadt family collection contains family papers and material relating to the F. Ronstadt Co. hardware store.
24.7 linear feet (approximately 9500 items).
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None
Biographical Note
A prominent pioneer family of Tucson, AZ; the Ronstadts of Tucson originated with Frederick J.M. Ronstadt's arrival in Tucson from Mexico in 1882 to work as an apprentice in the Dalton and Vasquez Wagon Shop. In 1888 he opened his own shop, serving as a blacksmith and custom wagon maker. The business grew to include leather goods, and eventually automobiles, farm machinery, and hardware goods. The F. Ronstadt Co. remained in business as a hardware store in Tucson until the 1980s, carried on by Ronstadt's sons Edward and Gilbert Ronstadt.
Frederick J.M. Ronstadt was active in Tucson civic life, including the Elks, Rotary, and Knights of Columbus. He was an early member of the Tucson Pioneer Historical Society, now the Arizona Historical Society. The Ronstadts are also known for their contribution to the cultural growth of Tucson. Frederick Ronstadt founded the Club Filarmónico de Tucson in 1889, and that musical tradition was carried on by his daughter Luisa Espinel and granddaughter Linda Ronstadt.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into four series: Business Records, Family Papers, Photographs, and Oversize. The Business Records are divided into three subseries. The Family Papers are divided into fifteen subseries. The Photographs are divided into three subseries. Oversize is divided into three subseries. In many cases original folder titles were retained.
Series 1: Business Records 1895-1977
Subseries: Finance
Subseries: Organizational History
Subseries: Inventories
Series 2: Family Papers 1802-1993
Subseries: Dalton, Henry
Subseries: Dominquez, Martin
Subseries: Lewis, Louise Dalton
Subseries: Milich, Miodrag
Subseries: Real Estate
Subseries: Ronstadt, Alfred
Subseries: Ronstadt, Alicia
Subseries: Ronstadt, Edward
Subseries: Ronstadt Family
Subseries: Ronstadt, Frederick A
Subseries: Ronstadt, II Frederick A
Subseries: Ronstadt, Frederick JM
Subseries: Ronstadt, Luisa
Subseries: Ronstadt, Lupe Dalton
Subseries: Zepada, José Maria
Series 3: Photographs 1870-1979
Subseries: Business
Subseries: Family
Subseries: General
Series 4: Oversize 1894-1958
Subseries: Business Records
Subseries: Family Papers
Subseries: Photographs
Scope and Content Note
The Ronstadt Family Collection contains family papers and material relating to the F. Ronstadt Co. hardware store. The Family Papers are organized by individual/subject and include biographical information, correspondence, diaries, personal notebooks, and publications. The Business Records consist of primarily financial and administrative documents, including store credit applications, merchandise inventories and ledgers, and organizational history of the Tucson hardware store. Photographs contain family and business images.
Related Materials
The published edition of Frederick JM Ronstadt's memoir is catalogued separately. The Records of the Club Filarmónico Tucsonense, of which Frederick J.M. Ronstadt was a founding member, are a related but separate collection.
Call # F819.T99 M56 1993 Borderman: Memoirs of Federico José María Ronstadt, By Federico Jose Maria Ronstadt
MS 385: Records of the Club Filarmónico Tucsonense. ca. 1890-1899
Access Terms
Rondstadt family -- Archives
Ronstadt, Federico José María
Ronstadt, Edward F., 1916-
Mexican Americans -- Social life and customs -- Arizona -- Tucson
Container List
- Series 1: Business Records 1895-1977, 7 linear feet (approximately 3485 items).
  The Business Records series is divided into three subseries.
  Finance (1935-1949) contains financial records from the F. Ronstadt Co. It is comprised of mostly store credit applications.
  Organizational History (1895-1940) is comprised of various documents related to the incorporation and administration of the company, as well as marketing and advertising material.
  Inventories (1971-1977) are large bound volumes of store merchandise inventories from the Ronstadt hardware store.
  - Subseries: Finance, 1935-1949
    - Corporate reorganization. 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Credit applications A. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
    - Credit applications B. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5-8)
    - Credit applications C. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9-12)
    - Credit applications D. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
    - Credit applications E. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Credit applications F. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
    - Credit applications G. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 19-21)
    - Credit applications H. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 22-25)
    - Credit applications I. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Credit applications J. 1935-1949 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Credit applications K. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
    - Credit applications L. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 3-6)
    - Credit applications Mc. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Credit applications M. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 8-12)
    - Credit applications N. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)
    - Credit applications O. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Credit applications P. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 16-18)
    - Credit applications Q. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Credit applications R. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 20-22)
    - Credit applications S. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 23-28)
    - Credit applications T. 1935-1949 (Box 2, Folder 29-32)
    - Credit applications U. 1935-1949 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Credit applications V. 1935-1949 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Credit applications W. 1935-1949 (Box 3, Folder 3-7)
    - Credit applications XYZ. 1935-1949 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - General. 1903-1928 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Subseries: Organizational History, 1895-1940
    - Articles of Incorporation. 1898-1899 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Factbook. 1913 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Marketing and advertising material. 1895-1940 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Subseries: Inventories, 1971-1977
    - "M". 1971 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - "H" pp. 1-582. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - "H" pp. 583-705. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Hardware pp. 1-489. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Sporting goods pp. 490-556. 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Housewares pp. 557-671. 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Machinery. 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Machinery. 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Hardware- housewares. 1973 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Parts. 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Hardware, housewares, sporting goods, paint. 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Machine pumps, plastic pipe. 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Hardware, housewares, sporting goods pp1-562. 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Pump, ind. machinery, farm machinery, plastic pipe pp. 1-32, parts pp. 1-335. 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Parts, pump, ind. & farm machinery, plastic pipe pp. 1-374. 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Hardware, sporting goods, paint, housewares, pp. 1-612. 1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Machinery pp. 1-337, pp. 1-31. 1977 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Hardware pp. 1-628. 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Series 2: family papers, 1802-1993, 4.2 linear feet (approximately 5000 items).
  - Subseries: Dalton, Henry, 1802-1958
    Grandfather of Lupe Dalton Ronstadt. Includes biographical information and a list of his descendants.
    - Biography and family history. 1802-1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Subseries: Dominguez, Martin. 1936-1951
    First husband of Alicia Ronstadt. They were married in Spain in the 1920s, but later divorced. For a time, Dominguez was trapped in Cuba attempting to return to the United States from Spain, as is reflected in his correspondence.
    - Correspondence. 1936-1951 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Subseries: Lewis, Louise Dalton, 1952
    Sister of Lupe Dalton Ronstadt. Interview by Edward Ronstadt about her life experiences.
    - Interview. 1952 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Subseries: Milich, Miodrag, 1949-1958
    Husband of Alicia Ronstadt, who fled to the United States as a refugee from Eastern Europe in the 1950s. His papers include documents legalizing his entry and stay in the US.
    - Official documents. 1949-1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Subseries: Real Estate, 1892-1963
    Documents relating to specific property owned by the Ronstadt family, and real estate investments and companies they were involved in.
    - Arizona- Mexico Land co. 1903-1926 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Las Delicias well. 1930-1938 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Insurance title abstract. 1892-1931 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Ranch properties. 1935-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Alfred, 1940
    Son of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt. Includes biographical information.
    - Biographical File. 1940 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Alicia, 1901-1979
    Daughter of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt. Primarily includes correspondence, with material related to her careers as an art dealer and Spanish teacher, and personal mementos.
    - Address cards. (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Autograph book- To Colette. 1923-1925 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Autograph book- To Alicia (1 of 2). 1954 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Autograph book- To Alicia (2 of 2). 1944-1951 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Biographical file. 1937-1968 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Business transactions. 1932-1934 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Collected postcards. 1938-1955 (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
    - Collected pamphlets. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence A-B. 1947-1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence C. 1937-1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence D-F. 1948-1972 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence G-J. 1936-1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence K-O. 1929-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence P-Y. 1938-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence- death of Laudelino Moreno. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence- death of Luisa. 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence- postcards. 1925-1975 (Box 7, Folder 15-17)
    - Correspondence- Relaciones book. 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- Ronstadt family. 1936-1979 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence- to siblings. 1927-1937 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Education materials. 1942-1965 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Programs. 1946-1963 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Religious mementos. 1901-1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Spanish report. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Stamps and postmarks. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Edward, 1933-1976
    Son of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt who succeeded his father in the family business. Primarily includes his research on the subject of his family and the Tucson area. Contains correspondence, speeches, and publications.
    - Biographical file. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence- research. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Family history. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Publications. 1933-1975 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Spanish history research. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Speech file. 1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt family, 1901-1981
    Includes general biographical information about the history of the family as a whole, as well as key individuals.
    - Biographical file. 1901-1981 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Frederick A., 1855-1883
    Father of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt. Born and raised in Germany, he immigrated to Mexico where he married and raised a family. Contains biographical information and correspondence.
    - Biographical file. 1855-1883 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence. 1866-1881 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt II, Frederick A., 1917-1941
    Son of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt. Includes correspondence and documents related to his business interests in Spain.
    - Correspondence. 1917-1942 (Box 7, Folder 35-36)
    - Correspondence- Hills Bros. coffee. 1940 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Official document. 1927 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Spanish business receipts. 1932-1939 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Frederick J.M., 1879-1993
    Papers comprise the bulk of this subseries, primarily consisting of correspondence, private ledgers, and drafts of his memoir Borderman.
    - Address book. 1927 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Awards and certificates. 1883-1944 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Biographical file. 1888-1971 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Borderman draft. (Box 7, Folder 43-47)
    - Borderman draft. (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Borderman proof. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
    - Carriage Builders Technical School papers. 1901-1903 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence- A. 1938-1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence- B. 1937-1952 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence- C. 1938-1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence- D. 1936-1953 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence- E-F. 1888-1953 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence- G. 1889-1953 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence- H. 1931-1953 (Box 8, Folder 12-13)
    - Correspondence- I-K. 1933-1952 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence- L. 1932-1950 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence- M. 1892-1951 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence- N-P. 1938-1952 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence- R. 1886-1950 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- S. 1938-1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence- T. 1932-1950 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence- U-V. 1931-1946 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence- W. 1938-1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence- Z. 1935-1950 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, Redondo family. 1900-1922 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Alfred. 1938-1951 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Alicia. 1937-1953 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, Levin, Emily Ronstadt. 1902 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Frederick A. 1883-1888 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt II, Frederick A. 1937-1947 (Box 8, Folder 29-31)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt Jr., Frederick A. 1938-1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Gilbert and Ruthmary. 1944-1945 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Laura. 1938-1953 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Luisa. 1921-1952 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Lupe Dalton. 1903 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, Margarita Redondo. 1882-1901 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, Ronstadt, William. 1937-1953 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Date book- honeymoon. 1904 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Family histories- Dalton. (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Family histories- Levin. 1834-1902 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Family histories- Redondo. 1852-1921 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Family histories- Ronstadt. 1882-1980 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Memorandum notebook. 1920 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Musical interest. 1890-1940 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Notebooks, general. 1941-1952 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Notebook, personal. 1886-1888 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Official documents. 1897-1919 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Private accounts book #1. 1900-1920 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Private ledger #2. 1918-1929 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Private ledger #3. 1921-1934 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Richardson- Zepada matter. 1915-1950 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Sketchbook- wagons. 1883 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Speeches and talks. 1884-1953 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Store customer notebook. 1900-1912 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Things I remember. 1952 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Tucson history. 1879-1955 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Luisa, 1908-1961
    Daughter of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt, also known as Luisa Espinel. Includes material related to her profession, as well as diaries and mementos from her school years.
    - Biographical file. 1918-1935 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Casa de Adobe. 1954-1956 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Diary excerpts. 1912-1918 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Diary- retreat notes. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Diary- school days. 1908-1911 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Conversational Spanish class notes. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence- professional development. 1928-1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence- scrapbook. 1927-1935 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Cantos de Mi Padre note. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Lucy Cobb Institute programs. 1923-1925 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Mementos. 1910-1912 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Mount Carmel Academy reunion. 1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Professional research materials. 1934-1957 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - The Promise, translation. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Publications and press releases. 1931-1945 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Recital programs. 1916-1959 (Box 9, Folder 28-30)
    - Recital programs- other artists. 1931-1954 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Sheet Music- original compositions and arrangements. 1939-1961 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Subseries: Ronstadt, Lupe Dalton, 1921-1972
    Second wife of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt and mother of sons Alfred, Edward, Gilbert, and William. Includes correspondence and publications.
    - Correspondence. 1921-1972 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Publications. 1937 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Subseries: Zepada, Jesus Maria, 1862-1939
    Brother-in-law of Frederick J.M. Ronstadt. Includes biographical information.
    - Biographical File. 1862-1939 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Series 3: Photographs, 1870-1979, 1 linear foot (approximately 1000 items).
  The Photographs series is divided into three subseries:
  Business (1887-1950) consists of photos of various store locations and merchandise sold. Including store interiors and exteriors, catalog goods, and employees.
  Family (1870-1979) primarily consists of photos of family and friends of the Ronstadt family including candid and professional images, in group and individual settings. Contains original daguerreotype and tintype images. Also includes, images of interests related to the Ronstadt family, such as their real estate holdings, special events, and publications.
  General (1894-1977) includes images of the American Southwest, Northern Mexico and the Baja Peninsula, and of United States Troops stationed on the US-Mexico border.
  - Subseries: Business, 1887-1950
    - Automobiles. 1918-1920 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Catalog images- saddles and chaps. 1913 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - F. Ronstadt Co. employees. 1900-1916 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - F. Ronstadt Co. store interiors. 1901-1928 (Box 10, Folder 5-8)
    - F. Ronstadt Co. store exteriors. 1887-1950 (Box 10, Folder 9-10)
    - Wagons. 1912 (Box 10, Folder 11-14)
    - Wagons scrapbook. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Subseries: Family, 1870-1979
    - Booklet- Daltons, Ronstadts, Smiths. 1904 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Colette album loose photos. 1948 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Dalton family. 1878-1890 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Early family photos. 1864-1904 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Newspaper article and photos. 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Party. 1954 (Box 10, Folder 21-23)
    - Real estate. 1903-1920 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Redondo, Jose Maria. 1890-1899 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Ronstadt, Alfred, Edward, Gilbert, and William. 1927-1972 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Ronstadt, Alicia. 1900-1966 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Ronstadt, Alfred. 1928 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Ronstadt, Edward and family. 1919-1979 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Ronstadt, Frederick A. 1870-1879 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Ronstadt, Frederick J.M. and family. 1920-1943 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Ronstadt, Frederick J.M. 1873-1950 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Ronstadt, Gilbert and family. 1922-1952 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Ronstadt, Luisa. 1911-1955 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Ronstadt, Lupe Dalton. 1895-1938 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Smith, Harold and Marguerite Ronstadt. 1905-1928 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Vasquez family. 1870-1879 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Subseries: General, 1894-1977
    - Arizona- Mexico buildings. 1894-1977 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Baja, California. (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous places. (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Tucson, Arizona. 1908-1972 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - United States troops on the border. 1922-1932 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Series 4: Oversize, 1894-1958, 1 linear foot (approximately 1000 items).
  The Oversize series is divided into three subseries.
  Business (1894-1958) contains mostly large ledger and minute books from both the store and the administrative bodies of the company. Includes financial and organizational records.
  Family (1927-1932) is comprised of material relating to Edward Ronstadt's research into former family property and connections in California, and scrapbooks of newspaper clippings for performer Luisa (Espinel) Ronstadt.
  Photographs (1904-1952) contains images of the store exterior in the early twentieth century and catalog images of wagons for sale. Family photos include large professional portraits of Frederick JM Ronstadt, and his niece Marguerite, and an album compiled by family friend Colette.
  - Business Records, 1894-1958
    - Board of Directors minute book. 1904-1930 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Check register book. 1950-1955 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Check register- salary records. 1956-1958 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Stock certificate book. 1921-1930 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Stockholders minute book. 1930-1935 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Sales totals register. 1907-1935 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Statements of loss and gain. 1913 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Store credit ledger. 1894-1898 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Ronstadt, Edward, family history- California ranchos. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ronstadt, Luisa, scrapbook- newspaper clippings. 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Ronstadt, Luisa, scrapbook- newspaper clippings and programs. 1927-1932 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Subseries: photographs, 1904-1952
    - Business records, store exterior. 1904 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Business records, wagons. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Family Papers, Ronstadt, Frederick J.M. 1952 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Family papers, Ronstadt, Marguerite (Smith). 1924 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Family apers, Scrapbook- photos from Colette. 1948 (Box 18, Folder 5)